export const response = {
  subject: 'mathematics',
  subTopic: 'algebra',
  chapters: [
    {
      id: 1,
      name: 'Chapter One',
      score: '80',
      timeTaken: '35min 20sec',
      totalTime: '40',
      accuracyAnalysis: {
        correct: 13,
        incorrect: 4,
        unattempted: 3,
      },
      caseStudy: {
        local: {
          total: 2,
          attempted: 0,
          percentage: 0,
        },
        global: {
          total: 2,
          attempted: 1,
          percentage: 50,
        },
        interface: {
          total: 2,
          attempted: 2,
          percentage: 100,
        },
      },
      difficultyAnalysis: {
        easy: 40,
        normal: 70,
        hard: 28,
      },
      questions: [
        {
          id: 1,
          question: '1 Statements and plants need sunlight to grow. Raju said, "I think mixing red paint with yellow paint gives green color." Mahesh said, "No, my friend said mixing red color with yellow color gives blue color." Ram took two drops of red paint and two drops of yellow paint. He got orange color. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint and two drops of yellow paint. He got orange color. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'one',
          userSelected: 'one',
          status: "correct"
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 2',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'two',
          userSelected: null,
          status: "unattempted"
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 3',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'four',
          userSelected: 'three',
          status: "incorrect"
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 4',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'two',
          userSelected: 'two',
          status: "correct"
        },
        {
          id: 5,
          question: 'Q5 Statements and plants need sunlight to grow. Raju said, "I think mixing red paint with yellow paint gives green color." Mahesh said, "No, my friend said mixing red color with yellow color gives blue color." Ram took two drops of red paint and two drops of yellow paint. He got orange color. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint and two drops of yellow paint. He got orange color. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
         correctOption: 'four',
          userSelected: 'three',
          status: "incorrect"
        },
        {
          id: 6,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 6',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'two',
          userSelected: null,
          status: "unattempted"
        },
        {
          id: 7,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 7',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'four',
          userSelected: 'three',
          status: "incorrect"
        },
        {
          id: 8,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 8',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'two',
          userSelected: 'two',
          status: "correct"
        },
        
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      name: 'Chapter Two',
      score: '20',
      timeTaken: '30min 20sec',
      totalTime: '30',
      accuracyAnalysis: {
        correct: 10,
        incorrect: 7,
        unattempted: 3,
      },
      caseStudy: {
        local: {
          total: 2,
          attempted: 0,
          percentage: 0,
        },
        global: {
          total: 2,
          attempted: 1,
          percentage: 50,
        },
        interface: {
          total: 2,
          attempted: 2,
          percentage: 100,
        },
      },
      difficultyAnalysis: {
        easy: 40,
        normal: 70,
        hard: 28,
      },
      questions: [
        {
          id: 1,
          question: '1 Statements and plants need sunlight to grow. Raju said, "I think mixing red paint with yellow paint gives green color." Mahesh said, "No, my friend said mixing red color with yellow color gives blue color." Ram took two drops of red paint and two drops of yellow paint. He got orange color. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint and two drops of yellow paint. He got orange color. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'one',
          userSelected: 'one',
          status: "correct"
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 2',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'two',
          userSelected: null,
          status: "unattempted"
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 3',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'four',
          userSelected: 'three',
          status: "incorrect"
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 4',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'two',
          userSelected: 'two',
          status: "correct"
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      name: 'Chapter Three',
      score: '50',
      timeTaken: '40min 10sec',
      totalTime: '45',
      accuracyAnalysis: {
        correct: 13,
        incorrect: 2,
        unattempted: 5,
      },
      caseStudy: {
        local: {
          total: 3,
          attempted: 1,
          percentage: 33.33,
        },
        global: {
          total: 3,
          attempted: 2,
          percentage: 66.67,
        },
        interface: {
          total: 3,
          attempted: 3,
          percentage: 100,
        },
      },
      difficultyAnalysis: {
        easy: 30,
        normal: 60,
        hard: 10,
      },
      questions: [
        {
          id: 1,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 1 in Chapter Three',
          explanation: "This is the explanation for question 1 in Chapter Three.",
          options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
          correctOption: 'B',
          userSelected: 'A',
          status: "incorrect"
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 2 in Chapter Three',
          explanation: "This is the explanation for question 2 in Chapter Three.",
          options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
          correctOption: 'D',
          userSelected: 'D',
          status: "correct"
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 3 in Chapter Three',
          explanation: "This is the explanation for question 3 in Chapter Three.",
          options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
          correctOption: 'C',
          userSelected: null,
          status: "unattempted"
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 4 in Chapter Three',
          explanation: "This is the explanation for question 4 in Chapter Three.",
          options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
          correctOption: 'A',
          userSelected: 'B',
          status: "incorrect"
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      name: 'Chapter Four',
      score: '80',
      timeTaken: '35min 20sec',
      totalTime: '40',
      accuracyAnalysis: {
        correct: 13,
        incorrect: 4,
        unattempted: 3,
      },
      caseStudy: {
        local: {
          total: 2,
          attempted: 0,
          percentage: 0,
        },
        global: {
          total: 2,
          attempted: 1,
          percentage: 50,
        },
        interface: {
          total: 2,
          attempted: 2,
          percentage: 100,
        },
      },
      difficultyAnalysis: {
        easy: 40,
        normal: 70,
        hard: 28,
      },
      questions: [
        {
          id: 1,
          question: '1 Statements and plants need sunlight to grow. Raju said, "I think mixing red paint with yellow paint gives green color." Mahesh said, "No, my friend said mixing red color with yellow color gives blue color." Ram took two drops of red paint and two drops of yellow paint. He got orange color. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint and two drops of yellow paint. He got orange color. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'one',
          userSelected: 'one',
          status: "correct"
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 2',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'two',
          userSelected: null,
          status: "unattempted"
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 3',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'four',
          userSelected: 'three',
          status: "incorrect"
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 4',
          explanation: "Ram took two drops of red paint. Among the three of them, whose approach is correct?",
          options: ['one', 'two', 'three', 'four'],
          correctOption: 'two',
          userSelected: 'two',
          status: "correct"
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      name: 'Chapter Five',
      score: '70',
      timeTaken: '45min 40sec',
      totalTime: '50',
      accuracyAnalysis: {
        correct: 14,
        incorrect: 5,
        unattempted: 1,
      },
      caseStudy: {
        local: {
          total: 3,
          attempted: 2,
          percentage: 66.67,
        },
        global: {
          total: 3,
          attempted: 3,
          percentage: 100,
        },
        interface: {
          total: 3,
          attempted: 3,
          percentage: 100,
        },
      },
      difficultyAnalysis: {
        easy: 20,
        normal: 60,
        hard: 20,
      },
      questions: [
        {
          id: 1,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 1 in Chapter Five',
          explanation: "This is the explanation for question 1 in Chapter Five.",
          options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
          correctOption: 'C',
          userSelected: 'C',
          status: "correct"
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 2 in Chapter Five',
          explanation: "This is the explanation for question 2 in Chapter Five.",
          options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
          correctOption: 'B',
          userSelected: 'D',
          status: "incorrect"
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 3 in Chapter Five',
          explanation: "This is the explanation for question 3 in Chapter Five.",
          options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
          correctOption: 'A',
          userSelected: 'B',
          status: "incorrect"
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 4 in Chapter Five',
          explanation: "This is the explanation for question 4 in Chapter Five.",
          options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
          correctOption: 'C',
          userSelected: null,
          status: "unattempted"
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      name: 'Chapter Six',
      score: '90',
      timeTaken: '50min 15sec',
      totalTime: '55',
      accuracyAnalysis: {
        correct: 18,
        incorrect: 2,
        unattempted: 0,
      },
      caseStudy: {
        local: {
          total: 2,
          attempted: 1,
          percentage: 50,
        },
        global: {
          total: 2,
          attempted: 2,
          percentage: 100,
        },
        interface: {
          total: 2,
          attempted: 2,
          percentage: 100,
        },
      },
      difficultyAnalysis: {
        easy: 40,
        normal: 40,
        hard: 20,
      },
      questions: [
        {
          id: 1,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 1 in Chapter Six',
          explanation: "This is the explanation for question 1 in Chapter Six.",
          options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
          correctOption: 'B',
          userSelected: 'B',
          status: "correct"
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 2 in Chapter Six',
          explanation: "This is the explanation for question 2 in Chapter Six.",
          options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
          correctOption: 'A',
          userSelected: 'A',
          status: "correct"
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 3 in Chapter Six',
          explanation: "This is the explanation for question 3 in Chapter Six.",
          options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
          correctOption: 'D',
          userSelected: 'C',
          status: "incorrect"
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          question: 'What is the question? - question 4 in Chapter Six',
          explanation: "This is the explanation for question 4 in Chapter Six.",
          options: ['A', 'B', 'C', 'D'],
          correctOption: 'C',
          userSelected: 'C',
          status: "correct"
        },
      ]
    },
  ],
};
